Seidenberg, Jacob Arbitration files 5468
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Jacob Seidenberg Arbitration files
1947-1974
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Seidenberg, Jacob
5468
12 cubic feet
12 linear ft.
Arbitration decisions.
Files of the impartial arbitrator Jacob Seidenberg. Includes subject files, conciliation files, and fact-finding files.
5652942
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, June 07, 2013
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, April 03, 2015
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5031 A&B: Jacob Seidenberg Additional Arbitration Files 5032: Jacob Seidenberg Injunction Study 5175: Jacob Seidenberg Taft-Hartley Maritime Dispute Records 5194: Jacob Seidenberg Additional Files 5217: Jacob Seidenberg Additional Arbitration Case Files 5229: Jacob Seidenberg Additional records 5519: Jacob Seidenberg Additional Arbitration Files 5571: Jacob Seidenberg Additional Arbitration Files 5605: Jacob Seidenberg Additional Arbitration Records 5635: Jacob Seidenberg Additional Arbitration Files 5666: Jacob Seidenberg Additional Arbitration Files 5706: Jacob Seidenberg Additional Arbitration Files 5756: Jacob Seidenberg Additional Arbitration Files 5773: Jacob Seidenberg Additional Arbitration Files 5808: Jacob Seidenberg Additional Arbitration Files 5900: Jacob Seidenberg Additional Arbitration Files 5935: Jacob Seidenberg Additional Arbitration Files 5953: Jacob Seidenberg Additional Arbitration Records 5988: Jacob Seidenberg Additional Arbitration Files
Arbitration, Industrial--United States.; Labor disputes--United States.; Mediation and conciliation, Industrial--United States.; Seidenberg, Jacob, 1914-
5652942
- Local 18-L -L 0IU, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- IBT - Local 570 - AP Tea, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Oil Chemicals and atomic Int. Union and A.P., 1964 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- P.L. Brand No. 717 Apalachicola Northern Railroad Co., 1971 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- ALPA. Int. - Union ALPA Professional and Administration Employees, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Public Law Board No. 869, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Office and Professional Employees Union Local #2, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Supplement Agreement, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- American Oil Company vs. Lud. Oil Workers Virginia, 1962-1963 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- AAA 16 390031, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Public Law Board No. 413, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- IBT - Local 622 Balt. Overall Chroning Co. FMCS, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Bel-Craft Inc. vs. IUMSWA Local 28, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Nat'l Univ of Hospital and Nursing Home Employees - Local 1199E, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Bethlehem Steel vs. Iron Workers Local #768, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Bowaters Southern paper Corp. -IBEWU - FMCS, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Budd Co- UAW, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Award No. 3, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Award No. 4, 1968-1970 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Award No. 5, 1968-1971 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Award No. 6, 1967-1972 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Award No. 7, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Award No. 7, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Award No. 8, 1967-1972 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Burris Processing Co. vs. I,B.T. Local 876, 1963-1964 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Butler Mfg. vs. District 50, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Teamsters Local 311 - C.J. Langfelder, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- P.L. Board No. 365 vs. Cambria and Indiana Railroad Company, 1968-1969 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Board CL-19547, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Carroll County Board of Education, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- CL - 19547, 1970-1973 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- University of Delaware vs. American Federation of State County and Municipal Workers, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- P.L. Board No. 524, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- P.L. Board No. 525, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Eastern Airline vs. Flight, 1961-1963 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Eastern Airlines and ALPA Cases 59-63 101-63, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- EAL Case No. 80-70, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- EAL - ALDA - 1969 5-69 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- United Furniture Workers of America - Eastern Products, 1968-1969 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Special Board of Adjustment No. 455, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Special Board Adjustment No. 459, 1962-1963 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Award - SBA #459, 1961 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Grief Brothers Cooperage Corp., 1969 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Gypsum Hanfeld 187 - Local 311, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Hotel Assoc. of Washington, D.C. and Joint Executive Board, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Ex. Board Hotel and Past Employees, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Hotel + Restaurant Employees + Bartenders Int. Union - Madison Hotel, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Int. Nickel Company vs. United Steel Workers of America, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- United Steel Workers of America and K-D Mfg. Company, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- USWA - K-D Mfg. Co., 1972 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Lockheed Georgia and Aeronautical Machinists - FMCS, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Lockheed - Georgia co., 1963 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- 8BA # 739 - LIRN BR Carrier, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Int. Brotherhood of Electrical Workers -#603 vs. Metropolitan Edison Company, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Nashville BRDG., 1971 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Shopmen's Local #713, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Doeler-Jarvis vs. UAW - Local 1086, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- UTU - Norfolk Western P.L. Brand No. 838, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- OLIN Conductors - FMCS allied Industrial workers 6927, 1971-1972 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Orr + Sembower vs. USA, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Owens Yacht Division, 1963-1964 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Owens Yacht Division, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Patapsco and Back Rivers Railroad Company, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- P.L. Board No. 397 - Patapsco + Back River - UTU, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Penn Central - BLE - "Oklahoma Conditions, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- P.L. Board No. 307 - Penn Central - BLFE - (Southern Region), 1969 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Public Law Board No. 456 - Pullman Co- UTU, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- P.L. Brand No. 669 Award No. 1, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- P.L. Board #669 Award No. 2, 1966-1971 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- P.L. Brand # 669 Award No. 3, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- P.L. Board No. 669 Award No. 4, 1961 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- P.L. Board NO. 669 Award No. 5, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- P.L. Board No. 669 Award No. 6, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- P.L. Board No. 669 Award No. 8, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Award No. 13 P.L. Board #13, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Award #24 F-15921 P.L. Board #669, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- P.L. Board #669 Award No. 16 F-16759, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Award No. 20 F-15943 P.L. Board #669, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Award No. 21 F-15507, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Award No. 22 F-15766 P.L. #669, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Award #25 F-15557 P.L. Board #669, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Award #26 F-15949 P.L. Board #669, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 15)
- Award No. 27 F-15373 P.L. Board #669, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 16)
- Award No. 28 F-15876 P.L. Board #669, 1971-1972 (Box 10, Folder 17)
- Award No. 29 F-15332 P.L. Board #669, 1962-1970 (Box 10, Folder 18)
- Public Law Board No. 674 Penn Central (N.E.) - BLE, 1969-1971 (Box 10, Folder 19)
- Awards No. 5+6 (Dockets 6+8), 1969 (Box 10, Folder 20)
- Award NO. 7 (Docket NO. 7) PC -BCE P.L. Board No. 955, 1969-1972 (Box 10, Folder 21)
- P.L. Board 955 NH - BLE, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 22)
- P.L. Board 955 NA - BLE Award No. 11, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 23)
- P.L. Board 955 NH - BLE Award No. 10, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 24)
- Final Draft of Item 1162 - UTU and Penn Central Transportation Award no.1, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Item 1229 UTU and Penn Central Transportation Award no.2, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Item 1830 - UTU and Penn Central Transportation Award no.4, 1955-1956 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Item 1866 - UTU and Penn Central Transportation Award no.5, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Item 1933 - UTU and Penn Central Transportation Award no.6, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Item 2125 - UTU and Penn Central Transportation Award no.7, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Items 2207 - UTU and Penn Central Transportation Award no.8, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Item 2 - UTU and Penn Central Transportation Award no.9, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Item 3 - UTU and Penn Central Transportation Award no.10, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Item 1935 - UTU and Penn Central Transportation Award no.12, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Retail Store Employees Union vs. Peoples Drug Store, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Peoples Drug Store -, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- ALPA - Piedmont Airlines, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- PG County Bd. Of Ed., 1972 (Box 11, Folder 14)
- Radio Corp of America vs. American Federation of Technical Engineers, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- RCA Corp. vs. IKEW of America Local 103, 1964 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Ronson Corp of Delaware vs. Int. Assoc. of Machinists, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Retail Employees Union - Local 692 vs. Safeway Stores Inc., 1972 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- AAA (D.S.) 14 30 Schluderberg - Kurdle Co. - Arrangement Meat Cutters Local 117, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- P.L. Board No. 458 South Buffalo - UTU (T), 1968-1970 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- P.L. Board No. 682 South Buffalo PR - UTU (T), 1972 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Awards Nos. 1, 3, 5, 7, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Awards No. 4, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Award No. 6 - Ph.. Brand #682, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- P.L. Board No. 823, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Southern Railway System - BLE, 1965-1969 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Special Board of Adjustment, 1969-1970 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Central of Georgia Railway and Southern Railway Merger, 1969-1970 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Special Board of Adjustment NO. 608, 1965-1969 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Standard Oil Company - IBT - Local 311, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- District 50 - allied and Technical Worker vs. Thrifty Paper Boxes. Inc., 1972 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Union Pacific Pub A#1, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Union Pacific PLB A#2, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Union Pacific PLB A#3, 1954 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Union Pacific PLB A#4, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Union Pacific PLB A#5, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Union Pacific PLB A#6, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Union Pacific PLB A#7, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Award No. 1 - O.L. Board No. 900 - UP - BLE, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Award No. 2-5-10 UP- BLE P.L. Board No. 900, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Award No. 3 P.L. Board NO. 900, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Award No. 4 - P.L. Board No. 900, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- Navy Dept. and Nat'l Association Govt. Inspectors, 1963 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- United Steelworkers of America vs. Union Railroad Company Board No. 646, 1968-1971 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Maryl and State Teachers Assoc. (Worchester County), 1970 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- IUMSWA, Local #43 AFL - CIO + Washington Aluminum Co., 1963 (Box 16, Folder 8)
- York Gazette Company ANG, Local 218, 1969-1970 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Wage - Hair Assignment - January 1970 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Emergency Board No. 16 BLF+E Carriers, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- TA - Hearthy Board of Inquiry - 1971 (Box 17, Folder 3)
- Fourth Division 1968-1970 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Special Board of Adjustment No. 484 National Vacation Plan, 1963 (Box 17, Folder 5)
- SBA # 494 National Holiday Agreements (SUNA), 1957 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Emergency Board NO. 155, 1963 (Box 18, Folder 2)
- Emergency Board NO. 178, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 3)
- Public Law Board No. 321 - Burlington Northern, 1961 (Box 18, Folder 4)
- Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- R 41386, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 2)
- 41427, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 3)
- R 41386, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 4)
- Case No. 107 813A #570, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 5)
- Case No. 107, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 6)
- Case No. 116, 117 SBA# 5701, 1964-1968 (Box 19, Folder 7)
- Case No. 109, 110, 111, SBA # 570, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 8)
- SBA #570 Case No. 106, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 9)
- SBA #729 BRT v. NYC (Southern District), 1967-1968 (Box 19, Folder 10)
- Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Allied Workers of North America vs. Washington Beef and Provision Company, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 11)
- Lehigh Valley - BLE, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 12)
- Philadelphia Bethlehem + New England P.L. Board No. 144, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 13)
- P.L. # 144, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 14)
- R 41303, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 15)
- Books #1, 1947-1968 (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Books #2, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 2)
- Books #3, 1967 (Box 20, Folder 3)
- Award No. 1 P.L. 1191, 1971-1974 (Box 20, Folder 4)
- Award No. 2 P.L. 1191, 1966-1973 (Box 20, Folder 5)
- P.L. Board 1102, 1971-1972 (Box 20, Folder 6)
- IBEW - Local NO. 107 and Oklahoma Power + Light Co., 1968 (Box 20, Folder 7)
- P.L. Board No. 107 BRT and PATH, 1967 (Box 20, Folder 8)
- IAMU Anderson - Hickey Co., 1968 (Box 20, Folder 9)
- Texaco and Ocawlu Local 8, 1967-1968 (Box 20, Folder 10)
- Award No. 2 P.L. Bd 818, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 11)
- P.L. Board No. 818, 1968-1972 (Box 20, Folder 12)
- ORC+B and PRR Arbitration Agreement, 1967-1968 (Box 20, Folder 13)
- Award No. 3 P.L. Board #818, 1968-1972 (Box 20, Folder 14)
- Award NO. 4 P.L. Board vs. 818, 1953 (Box 20, Folder 15)
- Award NO. 5 P.L. Board no. 818, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 16)
- Award No. 6 P.L. Board No. 818, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 17)
- Award No. 7 P.L. Board NO. 818, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 18)
- Award No. 8 P.L. Board No. 818, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 19)
- Award No. 9 - P.L. Board No. 818, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 20)
- Award No. 10 - P.L. Bd. 818, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 21)
- P.L. Board No. 117 Award No. 1, 1968 (Box 20, Folder 22)
- P.L. Board NO. 117 - Award NO. 2, 1967 (Box 20, Folder 23)
- P.L. Board NO. 117 Award NO. 3, 1967 (Box 20, Folder 24)
- P.L. Board No. 117 Award NO. 4, 1967 (Box 20, Folder 25)
- P.L. Board NO. 117 Award NO. 5, 1967 (Box 20, Folder 26)
- United Transportation Union - Board Chairman, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 1)
- Public Law Board No. 757 The River Terminal Railway Company United Transportation Union, 1970-1972 (Box 21, Folder 2)
- Public Law Board NO. 757 The River Terminal Railway Company United Transportation Union, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 3)
- FMCS File G7 Q/5940 Lockheed - Georgia Company - AIW AFL-CIO, 1967-1968 (Box 21, Folder 4)
- BRT and Western Maryland Railroad Company, 1966-1967 (Box 21, Folder 5)
- Special Board of Adjustment No. 560 Maine Central vs. BRT, 1966-1967 (Box 21, Folder 6)
- P.L. Board NO. 46 EJE + ORCB, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 7)
- VERCO vs. IBEW FMCS 63A/1059, 1967-1968 (Box 21, Folder 8)
- TWU vs. PRR, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 9)
- SBA #718 Western Maryland vs. BLF+E, 1964-1967 (Box 21, Folder 10)
- Fourth Divison - MRAB 1966 (Box 21, Folder 11)
- Glade Spring Products Inc. and ACWA-AFL-CIO, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 12)
- United Mine Workers of America and FMC Corp., 1968 (Box 21, Folder 13)
- PRR - TWUA Blue Hog Arbitration, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 14)
- IBT. Local 570 - B.Green and Co. FMCS Fale 68A/967 - Discharge, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 15)
- ALPA - EAL - #34-6 Grievance, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 16)
- Lynchburg Foundry Company and United Steelworkers Local NO. 2556, 1967-1968 (Box 21, Folder 17)
- United Automobile Workers Local 354 Wayne Pump Division, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 18)
- P.L. #11 South Buffalo RR vs. BRT, 1969 (Box 21, Folder 19)
- Rubatex Corp. Local 240 - URW FMCS File 68A/ 357, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 20)
- FMCS Fill 67A/4755 Local #22 IBT and Ray Stone Transfer Corporation, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 21)
- Wash. Baltimore Newspaper Guild Local 35 The Washington Post Company, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 22)
- Washington Post Guild, 1966-1967 (Box 21, Folder 23)
- ALPA vs. Frontier Airlines ALPA Case NO. 7001 (Morris Grievance), 1967-1971 (Box 21, Folder 24)
- FMCS File 68A/3996 (Schaefer Brewing Co -1AM), 1968 (Box 21, Folder 25)
- Olin Mathewson Chemical Corp. (Aluminum Division) and Allied Industrial Workers RLS #4 FMCS 68A/3206, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 26)
- BLFE vs. Western Maryland Company, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 27)
- Int. Rosse of Iron Workers NO. 733 Nashville, 1967-1968 (Box 21, Folder 28)